[
	{
		"id": "java-1",
		"question": "What does this code segment print? <div class=\"code\">static void increment(int index) { <br> &ensp;index++; <br>} <br> <br>public static void main(String[] args){ <br>  &ensp;int i = 0; <br>  &ensp;increment(i); <br> &ensp;i++; <br>  &ensp;System.out.println(i); <br>}</div>",
		"correct_answer": "1",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"3",
			"0",
			"2"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "java-2",
		"question": "What class can use a method from another class without a visibility modifier?",
		"correct_answer": "Any class from the same package",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Any class",
			"Any class that extends this class",
			"Any class from any subpackage of this package"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "java-3",
		"question": "What is an unchecked exception?",
		"correct_answer": "An exception that extends RuntimeException of Error that you do not need to catch or rethrow",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"An exception that extends RuntimeException that you may catch but cannot rethrow",
			"An exception that can be of any type, and that you do not need to catch or rethrow",
			"An exception that extends RuntimeException that you cannot catch but can rethrow"
		],
		"fr": "https://blog.octo.com/la-gestion-des-exceptions-en-java/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-4",
		"question": "How can you add a method to an existing interface without having to modify the classes that already implement it?",
		"correct_answer": "You make this method a default method",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"You provide an implementation of this method in a separate static class",
			"You make this method an abstract class",
			"You cannot add a method to an interface without implementing in the existing implementing classes"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "java-5",
		"question": "What does a class need to do when it declares that it is implementing an interface?",
		"correct_answer": "It must be declared as abstract OR implement each of the interface's abstract methods, apart from the methods of the Object class.",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"It must implement each of the interface's abstract methods and override the default methods",
			"It must be declared as abstract",
			"It must implement each of the interface's abstract methods"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "java-6",
		"question": "What will be the output of the following program? <div class=\"code\"><p>public class MyFirst {</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;public static void main(String[] args) {</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; MyFirst obj =newMyFirst(n);</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;}</p><p><br></p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;static int a = 10;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;static int n;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;int b = 5;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;int c;</p><p><br></p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;public MyFirst(int m) {</p><p>&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp; System.out.println(a + &quot;, &quot; + b + &quot;, &quot; + c + &quot;, &quot; + n + &quot;, &quot;+m);</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;}</p><p><br></p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;// Instance Block</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;{</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; b= 30;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; n = 20;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;}</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;// Static Block</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;static {</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; a = 60;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp;}</p><p>}</p></div>",
		"correct_answer": " 60, 30, 0, 20, 0",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"10, 5, 0, 20, 0",
			"10, 30, 20",
			"60, 5, 0, 20"
		],
		"source":"https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-7",
		"question": "Which of the following option leads to the portability and security of Java?",
		"correct_answer": "Bytecode is executed by JVM",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"The applet makes the Java code secure and portable",
			"Use of exception handling",
			"Dynamic binding between objects"
		],
		"source":"https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-8",
		"question": "What is the return type of the hashCode() method in the Object class?",
		"correct_answer": "int",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Object",
			"long",
			"void"
		],
		"source":"https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-9",
		"question": "What does the expression float a = 35 / 0 return?",
		"correct_answer": "Infinity",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"0",
			"Not a Number",
			"Run time exception"
		],
		"source":"https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-10",
		"question": " Evaluate the following Java expression, if x=3, y=5, and z=10: <div class=\"code\">++z + y - y + z + x++ <div>",
		"correct_answer": "25",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"20",
			"23",
			"24"
		],
		"source":"https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-11",
		"question": "What will be the output of the following program? <div class=\"code\"><p>public class Test { &nbsp;</p><p>public static void main(String[] args) { &nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; int count = 1; &nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; while (count &lt;= 15) { &nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; System.out.println(count % 2 == 1 ?&quot;***&quot;: &quot;+++++&quot;); &nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; ++count; &nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; }</p><p>&nbsp; &nbsp; }</p><p>&nbsp;} &nbsp;</p><div>",
		"correct_answer": "8 times *** and 7 times +++++",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"15 times ***",
			"15 times +++++",
			"Both will print only once"
		],
		"source":"https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-12",
		"question": "Which of the following for loop declaration is not valid?",
		"correct_answer": "<div class=\"code\">for ( int i = 99; i >= 0; i / 9 )<div>",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"<div class=\"code\">for ( int i = 7; i <= 77; i += 7 )<div>",
			"<div class=\"code\">for ( int i = 20; i >= 2; - -i )<div>",
			"<div class=\"code\">for ( int i = 2; i <= 20; i = 2* i )<div>"
		],
		"source":"https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-13",
		"question": "Which of the following is true about the anonymous inner class?",
		"correct_answer": "It has no class name",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"It has only methods",
			"Objects can't be created",
			"It has a fixed class name"
		],
		"source":"https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-14",
		"question": "Which option is false about the final keyword?",
		"correct_answer": "A final class cannot extend other classes.",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"A final method cannot be overridden in its subclasses.",
			"A final class cannot be extended.",
			"A final method can be inherited."
		],
		"source":"https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-15",
		"question": "Given that Student is a class, how many reference variables and objects are created by the following code? <div class=\"code\"><p>Student studentName, studentId;</p><p>studentName = new Student();</p><p>Student stud_class = new Student();</p><div>",
		"correct_answer": "Three reference variables and two objects are created.",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"Two reference variables and two objects are created.",
			"One reference variable and two objects are created.",
			"Three reference variables and three objects are created."
		],
		"source":"https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	},
	{
		"id": "java-16",
		"question": "Which of the following is a valid syntax to synchronize the HashMap?",
		"correct_answer": "<div class=\"code\">Map m1 = Collections.synchronizedMap(hashMap); <div>",
		"incorrect_answers": [
			"<div class=\"code\"> Map m = hashMap.synchronizeMap();<div>",
			"<div class=\"code\"> HashMap map =hashMap.synchronizeMap();<div>",
			"<div class=\"code\"> Map m2 = Collection.synchronizeMap(hashMap);<div>"
		],
		"source":"https://www.javatpoint.com/"
	}

]